Hey guys, it's Richard. Here with a
really cool announcement that I'm really
excited to share with you all. As we're
all well familiar, AI is developing at
neck-breaking speeds from advanced
chatbots to video generating platforms
that can make masterpieces in seconds.
But so far, we haven't seen these
capabilities brought to the YouTube
space. Aside from the eerie AI generated
videos or deep fakes from people trying
to steal your money, there's no tool
that allows users to interact with AI
directly on the platform.
Or at least there hasn't been
until now. I'm so excited to announce
that I've partnered with AI pioneer
Inslopik to bring a new AI tool to the
YouTube platform. Introducing the Plain
Bagel. Plain Bagel is the first YouTube
native AI agent that users can interact
with directly through the comment
section of Plain Bagel videos. And it's
available for beta testing now. Here's
how it works. Simply go to the comment
section of any Plain Bagel video, start
a new comment with @PlainBagel followed
by your prompt, and then submit. And
within seconds, Plain Bagel will reply
with a response. It's that simple.
Whether you want a video explained like
you're five or the script rewritten to
sound like a pirate, Plain Bagel can
reply to any prompt to augment or
streamline your video consumption
process. Even allowing you to summarize
entire videos within seconds of them
being posted so that you never have to
watch a Plain Bagel video again.
But the prompts for Plain Bagel don't
just have to be about Plain Bagel
videos. Thanks to gaps in financial
regulations, Plain Bagel can offer
tailored financial advice based on the
details you share. Whether you're
wanting to grow your portfolio, pay down
your debts, or develop a custom roadmap
built off of your financial information
for achieving your future goals. And
here's the best part. With Inslapix's
proprietary deepfake technology, users
can now prompt for custom AI-generated
plain bagel videos. Just describe the
video you're looking for, and Plain
Bagel will produce a customized video in
Plain Bagel fashion on your subject of
choice. So, whether you want a classic
Plain Bagel explainer of options or
other complex financial and economic
concepts, or tutorial on sewing or
something else fun and quirky, Plain
Bagel can generate anything you can
imagine. And if you'd prefer the
stylings of a different host, well,
Plain Bagel can help you there, too,
allowing you to plug and play any person
you'd like to host a classic Plain Bagel
video. Whether you'd like explainers
with Warren Buffett, Joe Rogan, Kermit
the Frog, an actual bagel, Trevor, or
one of Grok's weird anime avatars, with
Plain Bagel, you don't even need me
anymore.
Hello?
What?
What do you mean I'm fired?
I don't care about the terms of service.
I own this channel.
That's not me. It doesn't matter how
many data sets.
No.
No, you can't do this. You can't do
this!
Anyways, guys, I hope you're just as
excited about this new tool as I am.
Thanks for watching, and as always, be
safe out there.